myorganicacres.com 2014-04-04

# 

**_**Garden Fresh Co-op’s Privacy Policy**_**

**General**

_Garden Fresh Co-op_ thinks your privacy is important. Please read this section of our website to learn more about Garden Fresh Co-op's philosophy and privacy policy. We understand that the protection of privacy is a major concern to many of our customers. Garden Fresh Co-op is working hard to gain your trust by selling only the highest quality foods and products, and we want to do everything reasonably possible to keep your trust. To build on our relationship, Garden Fresh Co-op wants you to understand a little bit about how our website interacts with visitors and how we will use any information gathered when you visit our website. By using our services and viewing this Site, you are consenting to the information collection, use and disclosure practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Types of Information Gathered**

Garden Fresh Co-op may gather the following types of information: (1) personal information given voluntarily while using a feature of this website, for example, during a registration process or purchase, including name, address, phone number, e-mail address, birth date; financial information, such as credit card number; (2) information gathered as a result of voluntary participation in a survey or poll, or when communicating with our webmaster or customer service Team Members; and (3) information gathered automatically when visitors visit our website.

Garden Fresh Co-op will not sell or otherwise share personally identifying information with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services to you at your request, or as required by law. Garden Fresh Co-op will share this information with certain business partners to provide requested service that we do not provide directly. Garden Fresh Co-op will only share personally identifying information with these business partners if they agree not to disclose the information to other parties and agree not to use this information to solicit. 

Garden Fresh Co-op may share aggregate data collected through its website that does not personally identify any party with our research partner, and may from time to time share this type data with other business partners.

Garden Fresh Co-op may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

Also, if you participate in any blog or other online forum on our Site, any personal information that you post on the website may be shared with other participants in the forum. In any of these situations, the recipient of the personal information may be located in the United States or another jurisdiction that may not provide an equivalent level of data protection to the laws in your home country. 

**Registration**

In order for you to receive specific benefits of our website you may first be asked to supply certain information such as your zip code. Garden Fresh Co-op wants to supply you with information that benefits you and the more relevant information we have about you the better we are able to do this. 

Garden Fresh Co-op currently has an electronic newsletter and may launch similar products in the future. If you choose to receive our electronic newsletter, you will be asked for certain information so that we can customize your newsletter to suit your needs. Upon registering for the electronic newsletter, you will be asked for your name, email address, zip code, and other information specified in the enrollment process. You may be asked to tell us a little about your interests, including but not limited to, what sorts of articles you like to read, the sorts of wellness choices you currently make, and other questions of this nature. This information is used to deliver you a personalized electronic newsletter that we believe will be of interest to you. The more of this information you choose to share with us, the better we can craft a newsletter specifically for you. 

If you choose not to share information with us the newsletter will simply be more generic. For example, if you are primarily interested in articles about the environment, we can't deliver those to you unless you share your interest with us. Similarly, if you are a vegetarian and request recipes without disclosing this fact, we can't guarantee that all recipes we send you will be meat-free. Providing us with this type of information is voluntary and you may change supplied information or unsubscribe at any time from any portion or all of Garden Fresh Co-op's online services. 

**Surveys And Polls**

From time to time, Garden Fresh Co-op website users may be asked to participate in voluntary surveys and polls. As a part of this process you may be asked to supply personal information such as demographic information and lifestyle preferences. These surveys will be strictly voluntary and you can choose to disclose this information or not. 

**Cookies**

Garden Fresh Co-op may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, which may include your IP address, Garden Fresh Co-op's cookie information, session time, click path analysis, and the pages you request. Garden Fresh Co-op will only use this type of data in an aggregate form which does not identify you personally. 

**Updating Personal Information**

Garden Fresh Co-op understands that you may want to change or access your personal information. You may do so by following the directions on your e-newsletter. To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally-identifying information. 

**Garden Fresh Co-op's Use of Information**

Garden Fresh Co-op may use information gathered through its website for the following general purposes: (1) to customize content delivered to you; (2) to contact and provide service to you as well as improve the overall delivery of Garden Fresh Co-op's services; and (3) to conduct research for other purposes related to Garden Fresh Co-op's core business. In no case will Garden Fresh Co-op use personally identifying information for its own use or the use of any other party, except to provide the services you request or as required by law. Garden Fresh Co-op only reviews usage of our online content in the aggregate (meaning information summarized into large groups of users with no personally identifying information) to determine the most popular website features and to help us develop new content and service ideas.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

This document was last updated September, 2009. Garden Fresh Co-op may update this Privacy Policy at any time. If so, Garden Fresh Co-op will post the updated Privacy Policy on this site. Garden Fresh Co-op encourages you to review this privacy policy from time to time for any changes.

**Children**

Parents should always supervise their children while online. Garden Fresh Co-op's website is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. So that we may comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we ask that children under the age of thirteen not provide any personal information on this website.

**Links**

This website contains several links to other websites not controlled by Garden Fresh Co-op. We have attempted to choose our linked partners with great care; however, Garden Fresh Co-op is not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked site. You should read the privacy policy of each linked website to understand the related policy. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected through Garden Fresh Co-op's website. In addition, when you browse, they may place their own cookies on your computer and we do not control cookies placed on your computer by third parties whose links appear on our site.

**Security**

Garden Fresh Co-op has attempted to take all reasonable steps to have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in place to protect personal information gathered through this website. This includes compliance with related federal regulations and may include use of industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk.

**Questions and Comments**

Garden Fresh Co-op is always interested in what our customers have to say. If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:info@gardenfreshco-op.com).
